

## +971 50-351-6752

### bensaadfares@gmail.com



www.bensaad-fares.xyz

## About me.

Highly driven recent web and information system graduate. With a flair for creating elegant solutions in the least amount of time. Comes with successful experience in Backend Web development. Bringing deep knowledge of Digital Marketing and Web Design.

### Reference. ——

#### **Rector Office**

Abdelhamid Mehri University

P: (213) 317-75023

M: rectorat@univ-constantine2.dz

# FARES BENSAAD

Web Developer

Work Experience.

# INFODZ Groupe Web Developer

2021 - 2022

- Created built a full affiliate marketing web app for store management software. With proficient Frontend and Backend development, The application manages customer orders and the company's affiliated sellers.
- Fixed bugs from existing websites and implemented enhancements that significantly improved web functionality and speed.
- Created responsive web pages and dashboard for admin and resellers
- Build reusable code and components for future use.

# IZstore 2020-2021 Hardware Technician

 Maintained customer's computer systems and peripherals by installing, configuring, testing, troubleshooting, and repairing hardware.

 Provided in-store assistance to customers, browsing inventory and checking out items.

Education.	2018 - 2021
Abdelhamid Mehri University , Algeria	
<b>Bachelor Of Information Systems</b>	

# Languages \_\_\_\_\_

• Arabic: Native

· English: Intermediate.

• French: Intermediate

## Skills.

HTML, CSS,SCSS, Javascript	Animation	
React JS, Next JS	NodeJS	_
Database design	Figma/XD	
PHP	 Illustrator	